{
    "subject": "resource/United_States_Senate_election_in_Texas,_2006",
    "predicate": "ontology/startDate",
    "object": "2006-11-07",
    "human_readable": "The United States Senate election in Texas took place on November 7, 2006.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9663339853286743,
            "question": "Was there a US Senate election in Texas in 2006?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9563611745834351,
            "question": "What type of election took place in Texas on November 7, 2006?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9407148361206055,
            "question": "In which state did a Senate election occur on November 7, 2006?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9220197200775146,
            "question": "When did the United States Senate election in Texas take place?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8679834008216858,
            "question": "What year was the United States Senate election in Texas held?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8541792035102844,
            "question": "Is November 7th a significant date for US elections in Texas?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7782526612281799,
            "question": "On what date did a Texas Senate election occur?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7554804682731628,
            "question": "What month and day was the US Senate election in Texas held?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7407599687576294,
            "question": "November 7th is a date associated with which political event in Texas?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5016976594924927,
            "question": "Which government body was being elected in Texas in 2006?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The United States Senate election in Texas took place on November 7, 2006.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6213_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=November 7th is a date associated with which political event in Texas?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6213_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What month and day was the US Senate election in Texas held?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6213_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=On what date did a Texas Senate election occur?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6213_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6213_104.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6213_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6213_114.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6213_116.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6213_125.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6213_126.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6213_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6213_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6213_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6213_83.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON format with the answer:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports this triple. The document with file_path /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_6213/re-ranker-msmarco/10.txt mentions that \"The 2006 United States Senate election in Texas was held November 7, 2006.\" which confirms the date of the event."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provided contain information about the 2006 United States Senate election in Texas, which did indeed take place on November 7, 2006. Therefore, the statement \"The United States Senate election in Texas took place on November 7, 2006\" is supported by the given context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}